Hello friends, I am Kait Goswami, today I have
brought such information which can be useful to you.
Those who have filled the Plaza Wire IPO, please
tell me by commenting how you liked it.
I had already said that it is a good
IPO. It got listed today and it is listed around 80. There is an
upper circuit. Those who have
filled the IPO have got only
benefits. So friends, I have also brought some such
stocks, two stocks are bullish too, out of which
I can tell you anytime in the middle or at the end. Some companies are going to
announce dividend, some
companies are going to give split, so friends,
stay tuned till the end of the video. So friends, first let's
talk. The offer price of Plaza Wire IPO was
kept at ₹5000000.
Please do let me know by commenting. Yes friends,
now let's talk about those stocks which are going to
announce dividend and quarterly results. The first stock is
Lamia Bharat Limited. The share price is currently trading
around 222303. There is a meeting for dividend and quarterly
results on 14th October. Kels
India Limited share price is currently trading  It is
around 1125, there is a
meeting for dividend and quarterly results. On 15 October,
LNT Technology Service Limited share
price is currently trading
around ₹ 4788, there is a meeting for dividend and quarterly
results. On 17 October, III
Lord General Insurance Company Limited share
price is currently trading
around 1326, there is a meeting for dividend and quarterly
results. On 18 October, LNT
Dmitry Limited share price is currently trading, there is a
meeting for results. On 18 October, BCL
Limited share price is currently trading
around ₹ 20, it is giving a split in the ratio of 1:1, that is, if
you have one share of it,
you will get one share for free. The
meeting date is 18 October. So friends,
I had told you about bully shares,
one is Ro Mo Cup, which is currently trading
around 3100. The second bully stock is NMDC
Limited, it has given a return at 21.8 within
a year, it is currently trading
around 159. Friends, I have
analyzed this, I will tell you some  I am
not recommending whether you should buy or
sell it. You
can buy or sell it after analyzing it yourself. The third stock
is L&T Limited. This L&T company
operates in many places and is
also associated with many companies. Its share price is currently trading
around 3081. It is a
leading company in this market, which means you can trust it and your
money will not be lost in it.
Friends, please tell me in the comments how you liked my information.
I am not making any recommendations as to
which stock to buy or sell.
I have just told you the stock after analyzing it myself. Okay, if
you want to buy or sell a stock, then
analyze it yourself or
ask your broker. You can buy or sell as per your own understanding. So,
please let me
know by commenting. Like and share the video and
subscribe to my channel so that I
can share more such important information with you. Thank you.